Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jeff-bardin-3253a88 (LinkedIn) www.americanbusinessmedia.com/images/abm/CEBA/CEBA12/pdfs/ceba_finalists2.pdf (Portfolio) www.pop2life.com (Company)

Top Skills

New Media
Marketing Strategy
Account Management

Jeff Bardin

Experiential Marketing | Business Development | Account Management

Demarest, New Jersey, United States

Summary

Award-winning experiential sales and agency account leader with 30 year career in entertainment and media. Relationship builder, and sales hunter with proven track record of driving revenue, winning complex pitches and retaining clients. Proven ability to lead account/creative/strategy teams, close deals and secure creative partnerships. Highly competitive and creative self-starter with long term industry relationships and a dedicated following.

Experience

THE MRKT

Senior Vice President Experiential Marketing January 2023 - Present (2 years 2 months) Los Angeles, California, United States

THA Experiential

Senior Vice President Experiential and Brand Activation April 2021 - Present (3 years 11 months)

Los Angeles, California, United States

We are an accomplished, full-service brand experience agency led by a team who believes that creative ideas, flawless execution and remarkable customer service is everything. We help bold brands create meaningful engagement with consumers, influencers and press, and we'll do whatever it takes to make that happen.

Giant Spoon

Vice President, Experiential Account Director January 2019 - December 2020 (2 years)

Greater New York City Area

Condé Nast

Executive Director, Business Development Pop2Life March 2017 - January 2019 (1 year 11 months)

Pop2Life

6 years 11 months

SVP, Music + Business Development May 2014 - March 2017 (2 years 11 months)

Vice President / General Manager May 2010 - May 2014 (4 years 1 month)

Epic Records

Vice President Promotion and Operations September 2002 - April 2010 (7 years 8 months)

Develop and implement promotional, marketing, and advertising strategies with broadcast (radio, TV) and print (trade and consumer publications). Utilize strong strategic planning and execution skills; write advertising copy. Initiate ideas to create buzz around new product launches. Formulate and implement programs for radio contests, retail promotions, and event tie-ins. Manage daily operations of 20 person promotion team inclusive of all operations and financial planning for the entire department.

Elektra Records

Vice President Top 40 Promotion/Field Promotion October 1994 - September 2002 (8 years)

Regional Promotion Manager Chicago 1994-1997 Regional Promotion Manager New York 1997-1999 Direction Top 40 Promotion 1999-2000

VP Top 40 Field Promotion 2000-2002

Conceived and implemented promotional strategies for all Top 40 releases. Directed a 14-member promotional field team, managed daily operations, travel, artist events, regional strategy and planning, created advertising plans for artists in trade magazines, maintained and developed strong relationships with radio programmers nationwide to maximize radio airplay and sales volume.

EMI Records
Regional Promotion Manager

May 1991 - April 1994 (3 years)

Assistant SBK Records (New York 1991)

Local Promotion Manager in Chicago (1991-1992) and Cleveland (1993-94)

Implemented promotional strategies for radio station in my region, developed and maintained relationships with radio programmers to maximize radio airplay and sales volume.

Education

University of Maryland College Park
Bachelor of the Arts, Radio, TV and Film · (1987 - 1991)